<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<Mofy.Update.Title>Mofy Update Log</Mofy.Update.Title>

<Mofy.Update.label>
2023/04/09(0.1.4.0):
*Lowered the cost of some research studies.

*Added new research

*Added new buildings

*New weapons have been added.
All B.E.P races, including LittleFairy, can now be equipped.

2023/03/27(0.1.3.0):
*Fixed some graphics

*Separated FacialAnimation definitions into separate mods
To reduce the load at startup, I have separated FacialAnimation images and definitions into separate mods.
Please subscribe from the collection.

2023/03/05(0.1.2.0):
*Mofy's now appear dressed according to their roles

2023/01/31(0.1.1.3):
*Research race restrictions have been removed

*Added new equipment
Instead of adding the equipment of another race, this mod is now added by itself
Please note that you can no longer wear clothes of other races

*Armor values of various equipment have been adjusted

*New "Mofy Milkcocktail" has been added

*Some research has been removed

2023/01/30(0.1.1.2):
*Various statuses are no longer corrected based on age

2023/01/29(0.1.1.1):
*Increased the number of hairstyle types to 8

2023/01/15(0.1.1.0):
*Architect categories have been merged

2023/01/08(0.1.0.8):
*The setting was changed so that the gene of Biotech's appearance system cannot be adapted

2023/01/06(0.1.0.7):
*Corrected ear layer position

*Support for the function of fertility change through Biotech linkage of HAR

2022/11/23(0.1.0.4):
*Skin and hair colors are no longer changed by genes

*Adjusted behavior of source code

2022/11/11(0.1.0.3):
*Body shape graphics and costume graphics have been re-created

*Facial Animation elements have been adjusted.
Some data has been adjusted by re-creating graphics.
Some parts have been deleted. Please use mods such as CharacterEditer to correct them.

2022/10/31(0.1.0.2):
*The specification that made the face unique has been eliminated.
For existing saved data, please use CharacterEditer or other mods to correct this issue.

*Add Update Log(This Window)
</Mofy.Update.label>

</LanguageData>